already okay thank you very much for
已经可以了，非常感谢
everyone showing up for this talk
每个人都在参加这次演讲
obviously there's a lot of options and
显然有很多选择，
I'm particularly actually very
我真的特别非常
pleasantly surprised that I see a lot of
惊喜地看到我很多
familiar faces and a lot of speakers so
熟悉的面孔和很多演讲者
I think this is going to be an important
我认为这将是重要的
talk for all of us hopefully a timely
希望能及时与我们所有人交谈
one and perhaps a slightly over D one
一个，也许稍微超过D个
and honestly you know I would actually
老实说你知道我会
request that you consider delivering
要求您考虑交付
this talk so with that said let me talk
这么说，让我说话
a little bit about the motivation of
关于...的动机
this talk
这个演讲
this work is is part informative and
这项工作是有益的，并且
frankly part in the myth-busting I
坦率地说，我参与了破坏神话的活动
personally sort of got tired of the
个人有点厌倦了
propaganda that job ie somehow doesn't
宣传这份工作，即某种程度上不
run on the cloud right that the reality
在现实中在云上运行
is absolutely the opposite java runs
绝对是相反的java运行
extremely well on the cloud in fact it's
实际上，它在云上非常出色
probably one of the wealth supported
可能是支持的财富之一
technologies on the cloud today yes and
当今云技术是和
that's kind of sad that somehow we we
我们有点不知所措
are unable to get that narrative out
不能把叙述说出来
there are we gonna accomplish this in
我们将在
this one talk probably not right but at
这一讲可能不对，但在
least we have to start somewhere as a
至少我们必须从某个地方开始
Java EE community to change begin
Java EE社区开始改变
changing that narrative and being a
改变叙述并成为
little bit more balanced to that
有点平衡
narrative okay so that's the motivation
叙述好吧，这就是动机
for the talk I'll briefly introduce each
对于这次演讲，我将简要介绍每个
of one of us I have two really fantastic
我们当中的一个我有两个很棒
guys here working with me there they did
大家在这里和我一起工作
most of the heavy lifting of the of the
的大部分繁重工作
talk I'll tell you right now and I'm
我现在要告诉你，我
just so grateful for what these guys
真是感激这些家伙
have done for the talk but that's said
已经做了演讲，但是那是
I'll let Rodrigo and dry and introduce
我让罗德里戈干燥并介绍
themselves hello everybody my name is
大家好，大家好，我叫
Rodrigo Bartolotta I'm a senior manager
Rodrigo Bartolotta我是高级经理
with cap tech consulting I currently
我目前从事帽技术咨询
serve as the capability lead for the
充当能力领导
cloud service offering and obviously
云服务产品，显然
being involved with Java for many years
参与Java多年
yes I'm Ryan cupric I'm from the
是的，我是Ryan cupric，来自
system's I work in rnd on chemical
我在化学系工作
formulation software
配方软件
I run the Connecticut java uses
我运行康涅狄格州的Java使用
and co-author on a couple of the books
并合着了几本书
and my name is Reza Rahman I'm a senior
我叫Reza Rahman，我是大四
manager architect at CAPTA consulting
CAPTA Consulting的经理架构师
I've been involved in the Java ecosystem
我参与了Java生态系统
for a little while and yeah just here to
一会儿，是的，只是在这里
share share some stuff I need to and
分享分享一些我需要的东西，
this is a necessary evil slide obviously
这显然是必不可少的邪恶幻灯片
a Catholic is paying for both Rodrigo
一名天主教徒为罗德里戈（Rodrigo）支付
and my expenses to come here so
和我的费用来这里
basically we're proud to work for this
基本上，我们为此感到自豪
company it's really a great company it's
这真是一个伟大的公司
a nation it's a nationwide full-service
一个国家，它是全国性的全方位服务
IT consulting company wins a bunch of
IT咨询公司赢得了很多
awards all the time you know have some
一直奖励您知道的一些
fantastic people working for it like
很棒的人为它工作
Rodrigo here unlike myself okay so this
罗德里戈在这里不像我自己好吗，所以这
is roughly our agenda
大概是我们的议程
so we're firstly we're going to be
所以我们首先是
talking about Java EE on the cloud at a
在云上谈论Java EE
on as a bird's eye view then we're gonna
作为鸟瞰图，那么我们要
dive into basically each variant of Java
深入探讨Java的每个变体
EE running on the clock so respectively
EE分别在时钟上运行
if you've been around the cloud because
如果您去过云，因为
from the none of these acronyms that
这些首字母缩略词都没有
broadly surprises to you so
令您大吃一惊
infrastructure on a service docker or
服务泊坞窗上的基础架构或
containers as a service there's platform
集装箱即服务平台
as a service and also as a variant of
作为服务，也作为
that basically running Java EE on bare
基本上在裸机上运行Java EE
JVM based best solutions and finally
最后基于JVM的最佳解决方案
Java EE as fares or function as a
Java EE的功能或功能
service okay moving forward you know
服务还可以，您知道吗
Java EE in reality has been running on
实际上，Java EE一直在运行
the cloud forever in fact you know I
永远的云，其实你知道我
have a number of customers that have
有许多客户
been running Java EE on on the cloud
在云上运行Java EE
forever in fact it has been possible and
事实上，这永远是可能的，
people have been doing it since the Java
自Java以来​​人们一直在这样做
EE 6 timeframe so reality is this has
EE 6时间框架，这是现实
been going on for at least a good five
至少持续了好五个
years and and it's really sad that we
年，我们真的很难过
haven't gotten the narrative right yet
还没有叙述的权利
is especially you know what happened the
特别是你知道发生了什么
cloud deployments that I've seen on Java
我在Java上看到的云部署
EE so far by and large actually a lot of
到目前为止，EE实际上实际上有很多
it is is based deployments on AWS okay
它是基于AWS的部署
and I think that's reality for pretty
我认为这是现实
much most of the technologies out there
绝大部分技术
there are in fact incremental features
实际上有增量功能
that have been built into both Java EE 7
Java EE 7中都内置了这些功能
and Java 8 that benefit the cloud okay
和Java 8可以使云受益
and hopefully there's going to be a
希望会有一个
whole lot more
更多
coming up in the next releases of Java
将在Java的下一版本中发布
that specifically looks at the problem
专门研究问题
of what is it that you actually need in
您实际需要的是什么
cloud applications running Java
运行Java的云应用程序
applications running on various variants
在各种变体上运行的应用程序
of the cloud so it's running Java jaan
云，因此它正在运行Java jaan
on is is super easy right in fact
实际上是超级容易的
running any technology on is is super
运行任何技术都是超级好
easy so Java EE is is definitely not an
容易，所以Java EE绝对不是
exception there at all most of the you
你们大多数人都例外
know major IAEA's vendors it's very
知道国际原子能机构的主要供应商
super easy to do that namely the big
超级容易做到的就是大
clear is to players really being as
对于玩家来说，很明显的是
you're and AWS Java EE plays also
您和AWS Java EE一起玩
extremely well with docker okay this is
与码头工人非常好，好的，这是
another sort of fad item and and I
另一种时尚品，我
really I'd like to like to present a
我真的很想提出一个
session on that too and see how
会议也看到了如何
symbiotic the relationship actually is
关系实际上是共生的
between Java EE and Dockers so although
在Java EE和Docker之间
the containers are the service providers
容器是服务提供商
that are based on docker because Java EE
基于docker的Java Java EE
works was with which so were well with
作品与之相得益彰
docker it works well with those CAS
docker它与那些CAS配合得很好
based solutions as well and in fact
基于解决方案，实际上
there are many good pairs options as
有很多不错的配对选项，例如
well I mean really Java EE has the most
好吧，我的意思是说Java EE确实拥有最多的优势
amount of pairs options maybe with the
成对选项的数量可能与
exception of the bare metal JVM it's a
裸机JVM的例外
really a number of vendors that are
确实有许多供应商
focused on this you know some names are
专注于这个，你知道一些名字
openshift Oracle cloud bluemix ruku and
openshift Oracle云bluemix ruku和
jelastic and in fact I probably haven't
jelastic，实际上我可能没有
done done a favor done done just as 2/1
做完了，帮了忙，做了2/1
which thank you for reminding me problem
谢谢你提醒我的问题
which is it's s AP the s IP should have
IP应该是哪个AP
been in this list as well yes if we
也是在这个列表中，如果我们
recently certified the cloud platform
最近认证的云平台
against Java EE 7 so to make it up I'm
反对Java EE 7，所以要弥补
going to write a blog entry about it so
打算写一篇关于它的博客文章
and believe it or not you know Java EE
信不信由你，您知道Java EE
also can work extremely well in bare
裸机也可以很好地工作
metal JVM based bastrop platforms I
基于金属JVM的bastrop平台I
think this is a very interesting variant
认为这是一个非常有趣的变体
and I'm very happy that that part is
我很高兴那部分是
going to be covered by Ryan I think he's
会被瑞安覆盖，我认为他
gonna do a really good justice to that
会为此做一个很好的正义
because that's been one of the four
因为那是四个
points
点数
fear uncertainty in certain heat out
担心某些热度不确定
points is that okay
点是可以的
Java he doesn't work in those
Java，他不在那些
environments which is absolutely really
绝对是真的环境
not true as you'll see it is possible
事实并非如此，因为您会看到
because we have
因为我们有
a bunch of solutions out there that
一堆解决方案
allow Java applications to run on Java C
允许Java应用程序在Java C上运行
environments some of those names are
这些名称中的一些是
wild fly swarm payara micro coma Lizzie
野生苍蝇群payara微昏迷Lizzie
and WebSphere Liberty and even that
和WebSphere Liberty，甚至那个
isn't actually a comprehensive list okay
实际上不是一个完整的列表，可以
so I won't spend too much time on this
所以我不会花太多时间
slide let me explain what this slide
幻灯片让我解释一下这张幻灯片
actually is there's an application out
其实有一个应用程序
there called cargo tracker it's so the
有所谓的货物追踪器，所以
intent of that application is to
该应用程序的目的是
actually demonstrate solid design
实际展示坚实的设计
patterns namely two main drive in design
模式是设计中的两个主要驱动力
design patterns in Java applications
Java应用程序中的设计模式
it's a very handy application that I
这是我非常方便的应用程序
find to do all sorts of job eBay's demos
发现做各种工作eBay的演示
because it's a non-trivial application
因为这是一个不平凡的应用
it's about 10,000 lines of code it uses
它使用了大约10,000行代码
all kinds of Java API is JSF JPA u jb j
各种Java API都是JSF JPA u jb j
ms j batch and the like okay and we'll
ms j批处理之类的，好吧，我们将
probably adding those lists as well it
可能还要添加这些列表
was part of the job especially official
是工作的一部分，尤其是官员
Java EE project on java.net since that
从那以后在java.net上的Java EE项目
it's gone down it's a part of the github
它掉了，它是github的一部分
Java EE repositories but it's honestly
Java EE存储库，但说实话
not in very good shape so what we've
不是很好的状态，所以我们已经
done is we've hacked that thing and we
完成是我们已经破解了该东西，我们
now have a bearer on a project that we
现在有一个项目的承载者，我们
call j 3e j 3 dot github that io ok and
叫j 3e j 3 dot github io ok and
you'll find the former website that used
您会发现以前使用过的网站
to run on java.net running there
在运行在那里的java.net上运行
temporarily hopefully we fix this
暂时希望我们解决这个问题
problem and we make it part of the EE 4j
问题，我们将其纳入EE 4j
project instead of the j 3e
项目而不是j 3e
project okay so a Java EE on on on pairs
项目还可以，因此可以同时使用Java EE
on on is what is is is is simply your
在什么是是仅仅是你的
data center on somebody else's machine
别人机器上的数据中心
okay so what you get is basically the
好吧，所以您得到的基本上是
bare by-and-large
大体裸露
your bare bare hardware hardware level
您的裸机硬件级别
machine provisioning that you instead of
代替您的机器配置
ordering through your department and
通过您的部门订购
have some have your suicide mini install
有一些你的自杀迷你装
that for you well that somebody else
那对你很好，别人
does that stuff and you just click on
做那个东西，你只要点击
some stuff you know on a web page and it
您在网页上知道的一些东西
creates that bare metal machine for you
为您创造那台裸机
okay but most likely using some
可以，但是很可能使用一些
virtualization software or the hotel
虚拟化软件或酒店
than somebody physically buying the
而不是有人亲自购买
machine and sticking it in in the rack
机器并将其粘贴在机架中
by far this is the most popular path to
到目前为止，这是通往
the cloud that's the reality most people
大多数人都是现实的云
that are using cloud are really using
使用云计算的人实际上正在使用
iOS platforms and of course as you know
iOS平台，当然您也知道
I think as we all know the big you know
我想大家都知道
biggest players here are AWS and has you
AWS最大的参与者是您吗？
so Java as I said works extremely well
所以我说的Java非常好用
on is why wouldn't it it's just a yet
为什么不就这样呢
another server it just happens to be
另一个服务器恰好是
hosted on somebody else's machine so of
托管在别人的机器上
course you can set up a Java environment
当然可以设置一个Java环境
and deploy your application there above
并在上面部署您的应用程序
and beyond which we won't cover in to
除此之外，我们将不涉及
too much detail in addition to this most
除了这大部分之外，还有太多细节
of the big I as vendors actually have
我作为供应商的实际份额
specific support for Java EE api's in
Java EE API的特定支持
particular they provide images of Java
特别是他们提供Java的图像
EE application servers pre-built images
EE应用服务器预建映像
that you can much more easily deploy on
您可以更轻松地在
there is base platform so you go onto
有基础平台，所以您进入
Azure and you look at that as your image
Azure，您将其视为您的图像
library you'll see images for various
库，您将看到各种图像
job by application servers similarly
应用服务器的工作类似
there's ami is available on on AWS that
在AWS上有可用的AMI
is specifically target Java EE based
是专门针对基于Java EE的
application servers so actually this
应用服务器，所以实际上
blurs the line we won't cover it in
模糊了我们不会覆盖的线
great detail but this blurs the line
细节很棒，但这模糊了线条
between what is iis and what is pass
在iis和通过之间
actually the line is blurring more and
实际上，这条线越来越模糊了，
more right it's a literally a
更正确的是从字面上看
distinction between a few clicks as to
几次点击之间的区别
how categorizing something as IAS versus
如何将某物归类为IAS与
categorizing something as pass actually
实际上将某类归类为通过
I'm going to skip over the pros and cons
我将跳过优点和缺点
for the interest of time because we have
为了时间的利益，因为我们有
a ton of material to go through so I'm
一吨的材料要经过，所以我
going to not go over the pros and cons I
我不会去谈我的利弊
think for the most part we are
认为我们大部分是
understand this stuff will make the
了解这些东西会使
obviously the slides available to you
显然，您可以使用幻灯片
you can take a look at it so that all
你可以看看它，以便所有
said
说过
let me turn over turn it over to Rodrigo
让我把它交给罗德里戈
who is going to present our first demo
谁将展示我们的第一个演示
which is running Java EE on bare metal
在裸机上运行Java EE
iOS platforms
iOS平台
all right and as Reza said this is the
好的，正如Reza所说，这是
link so everything that we're covering
链接，以便我们涵盖的所有内容
is available in github and it's live
在github中可用并且它是实时的
shares so everybody can look into you
分享，这样每个人都可以看着你
know with more details so the first
知道更多细节，所以第一个
thing to go through
要经历的事情
you know infrastructure as a service
您知道基础架构即服务
we're starting with AWS and leveraging
我们从AWS开始，并充分利用
their ec2 service so anyone here
他们的ec2服务，所以这里的任何人
familiar with AWS ec2 I feel a few hands
熟悉AWS ec2，我觉得有些帮助
thank you
谢谢
so this is basically their virtual
所以这基本上是他们的虚拟
machine option as in already said you
机器选项已经说过了
can go with many other cloud providers
可以与许多其他云提供商一起使用
right so in this case most call
对，因此在这种情况下，大多数来电
providers they have some sort of
提供者，他们有某种
marketplace that was kind of mentioned
提到的市场
right so you can you know identify one
对，这样您就可以识别一个
application server of your choice and
您选择的应用服务器和
you know I'll start with one very you
你知道我会从一个非常你开始
know interesting so you can you know
知道有趣，所以你可以知道
search for one other choice you can have
寻找您可以拥有的另一选择
a pre-configured image and you start and
预先配置的映像，然后开始
your setup is in place or you can create
您的设置已经到位，或者您可以创建
your own right so let's suppose you
你自己的权利，让我们假设你
start your instance your virtual machine
启动您的实例您的虚拟机
you make our configuration and then
您进行配置，然后
create your own image you later on to
创建自己的图像，稍后再使用
reuse and that could be very interesting
重用，这可能非常有趣
you could look at it as an artifact
您可以将其视为人工制品
right through your pipeline as you move
在您移动时通过管道
around development on the way to
在开发的过程中
production you could very well have an
生产你很可能有一个
artifact that becomes your ami that
成为你的阿米的神器
spill teeny and package with several you
溢青少年和与几个你包
know pieces that will you know go
知道你会去的碎片
through your software lifecycle process
在您的软件生命周期过程中
I'm picking up something with Ubuntu you
我正在用Ubuntu接你
know nothing fancy here and we're
一无所知，我们在
choosing an instance type which is
选择一个实例类型
pretty much how much memory and CPU were
几乎有多少内存和CPU
going to give to this virtual machine
要给这个虚拟机
right our next step is network and these
对，我们的下一步是网络，这些
steps they're common to and any route or
他们常用的步骤以及任何路线或
machine type of service right so you
机器的服务类型对您来说
define a network you obviously in this
明确地定义一个网络
case we want to have public IP available
我们想拥有公共IP的情况
so we we enable that as this we're just
所以我们启用它，因为我们只是
taking the default configuration we give
采用我们给的默认配置
some storage so and and it's nice to see
所以有一些存储空间，很高兴看到
contrast and compare with other cloud
与其他云进行对比和比较
providers how they differentiate
提供者如何区分
you eye or their api's to make her life
你的眼睛或他们的api使她的生活
easier as a developer obviously naming
作为开发人员显然更容易命名
it something that it could be hard but
它可能很难，但是
it's very important because in this case
这很重要，因为在这种情况下
we're creating one specific route or
我们正在创建一条特定的路线，或者
machine but if you have hundreds of
机器，但如果您有数百个
thousands of them running in your
成千上万的
environment your workloads you need to
环境您需要的工作量
identify and easily try to figure out
识别并轻松尝试找出
what is doing what right so in this case
在这种情况下做什么是正确的
I'm just you know giving one some some
我只是你知道给一些
name so I'm gonna call this my you know
名字，所以我要叫这个我知道
Java one is it to instance demo then the
Java是实例演示然后
very next step is to identify a firewall
下一步是确定防火墙
which is in AWS terms is called a
在AWS术语中称为
security group
安全组
all right so for that you know we are
好的，因此您知道我们是
deploying a java application that's
部署一个
gonna be running port 8080 rial so that
将要运行8080端口里亚尔，以便
applications running on top of a
在一个应用程序上运行的应用程序
glassfish so we also want to enable the
玻璃鱼，所以我们也想启用
console admin on port 48 48 so obviously
控制台管理员在端口48 48上很明显
we need to make those available and and
我们需要提供这些资源，并且
for that reason I already have one
因此，我已经有一个
pre-configured pre set up security group
预配置的预设置安全组
here we review things we look at you
在这里，我们回顾一下我们在看你的东西
know there's no warning saying I'm gonna
知道没有警告说我要
pay for it
付钱
obviously one thing that's interesting
显然一件有趣的事
to note is all the cloud providers they
要注意的是他们所有的云提供商
have a free tier free get started type
有免费的免费入门类型
of approach all of them so it's really
接近所有人，所以真的
good to take one user case that you may
最好采取一个用户案例
have and go and explore across different
有和去探索不同
ones and then identify what's the best
然后确定什么才是最好的
option for you and and from here we
选项，从这里开始
launch that instance you have to have a
启动该实例，您必须有一个
security need to have your Pam files so
安全需要拥有您的Pam文件，以便
you can later on SSH you say launch and
您可以稍后在SSH上说启动和
AWS will do something behind the scenes
AWS将在幕后做些事情
obviously for interest of time I already
显然为了时间的利益，我已经
have one that's pre-configured it's
有一个预先配置的
already up and running and now that I
已经启动并运行，现在我
have you know exposed that IP address I
你知道暴露那个IP地址吗
can come in here and say well is there
可以进来说好在那里
anything running oh no right so let's
一切都在运行哦，不对，所以让我们
see if I have something on port 48 48
看看端口48上是否有东西
and apparently my internet connection is
显然我的互联网连接是
not helping me that never happens huh so
没有帮助我，永远不会发生
let's try again all right
让我们再试一次
so how can you go into the cloud without
所以如果没有
an internet connection huh but basically
可以上网，但是基本上
the idea is and that we'll see how this
想法是，我们将看到如何
is gonna shake with the next one every
会和下一个摇一摇
rigor I think the suggestion was to type
我认为建议是严格输入
in HTTP in front now the HTTP well let's
现在在前面的HTTP中，让我们
see thank you
看谢谢
there we go thank you very much so you
我们去了，非常感谢你，所以你
know this is you know the admin console
知道这就是你知道的管理控制台
that's available now if I change the
现在，如果我更改
port and obviously you can do whatever
港口，显然你可以做任何事情
you can do with any application server
您可以使用任何应用程序服务器
right there's nothing you know that that
没什么，你不知道
particular and if I go with my port 8080
特别是如果我使用8080端口
I should have a different message here
我应该在这里有一个不同的消息
pointing that saying that in all my
指着我所有的话
application server is up and running and
应用服务器已启动并正在运行，并且
eventually my cargo tracker application
最终我的货物跟踪器应用程序
alright but as it's lit loads and for
好吧，但是因为它点亮了负载
interest of time I think the the the
时间的利益，我认为
message here is behind the scene as you
您的消息在幕后
didn't see that I had to set up Java you
没看到我必须设置Java
didn't see that I had to set up
没看到我必须设置
GlassFish myself so the point being is
GlassFish我自己，所以重点是
there are no changes on my application
我的申请没有任何变化
was just a war file you need to think
只是你需要考虑的战争文件
about infrastructure right you need to
关于您需要的基础架构权利
think about network configuration
考虑网络配置
firewall so there are some takes there
防火墙，所以有一些需要
and you need to play a little bit of you
你需要扮演你的一小部分
know admin role in this scenario so
知道这种情况下的管理员角色
regardless of the call provider you pick
不管您选择的呼叫提供商
okay great so the next variant that
好吧，所以下一个变种
we're going to talk about is essentially
我们要谈论的本质上是
using Java EE with docker or containers
将Java EE与docker或容器一起使用
continue as a service platforms so what
继续作为服务平台，那么
has happened as Rodrigo mentioned and I
如罗德里戈所说，发生了
mentioned as well
也提到
Amazon has this concept of a mais okay
亚马逊有一个很好的概念
Amazon images saying similarly as your
亚马逊图像与您的说法相似
has a concept of images right the
对图像有正确的概念
reality is these are proprietary images
现实是这些是专有图像
specific to those platforms so if you
特定于那些平台，因此，如果您
want an image you've got to create an
想要创建一个图像
image and upload to their marketplace
图片并上传到他们的市场
somehow and etcetera etc so the reality
不知何故等等等等现实
is all that is kind of unnecessary
是所有不必要的
because docker is becoming such a
因为码头工人正变得如此
commodity right so instead of relying on
商品权利，所以不要依赖
their own proprietary ami systems what
他们自己专有的ami系统
the eye is providers and some of the
眼睛是提供者，而一些
best providers are doing is simply
最好的提供商所做的只是
saying hey we support docker right so
说嘿我们支持docker对吧
whatever your image may be get your
无论您的形象是什么，
image from docker hub or create your own
来自docker hub的镜像或创建自己的镜像
publish your own image into docker hub
将您自己的映像发布到docker hub
and use that to spin up a server
并使用它来启动服务器
instance and in fact multiple server
实例，实际上是多个服务器
instances in some cases so most of these
在某些情况下，大多数情况下
solutions that containers as a service
容器即服务的解决方案
solutions aren't just a matter of
解决方案不只是一个问题
spinning up individual instances with
与
docker images but they actually have
泊坞窗图片，但它们实际上有
orchestration built into into that as
编排内置于其中
well with all of the orchestration
与所有的编排很好
frameworks that are out there to support
可以支持的框架
dogger principally actually kubernetes
dogger主要实际上是kubernetes
is the most predominant one so most of
是最主要的
the cloud providers are supporting
云提供商正在支持
kubernetes and hence you can essentially
kubernetes，因此您基本上可以
spin up and down you know your cluster
上下旋转，你知道你的集群
and create a cluster and non-zeros in
并在其中创建一个群集和非零
just a simple instance in a relatively
只是相对而言的一个简单实例
automated fashion right so so that's
自动化的时尚，所以这是
what's called you know this new model
什么叫你知道这个新模型
called containers of none service and
称为无服务容器，
actually it's it's fairly prevalent
实际上这是相当普遍的
already so as I mentioned before Java EE
正如我在Java EE之前提到的那样
is actually a very good fit for confer
实际上是非常合适的
for the docker model it works extremely
对于docker模型，它的工作原理极为出色
well there are several reasons for that
嗯，有几个原因
so this you didn't use to be the case so
所以这不是你曾经的情况
some of the fun items around Java EE and
Java EE和
docker are basically outdated
码头工人基本上已经过时了
right so this was a
对，所以这是一个
the criticism that is there out there
那里的批评
you'll read on the internet basically
您基本上会在互联网上阅读
what they're trying to tell you is a
他们想告诉你的是
docker image is monolithic right so you
码头工人图像是整体的，所以你
want the docker image to be as small as
希望docker映像尽可能小
possible so that that monolithic docker
可能使那个整体式码头工人
image doesn't get too big and it's and
图像不会变得太大，而是
it doesn't get too difficult to deploy
部署不会太困难
and the like well guess what
以及类似的猜猜是什么
the docker guys have figured this out I
码头工人想通了
figure figure the problem because this
图因为这个问题
is not a solution there's not a problem
不是解决方案，没有问题
specific to Java EE but guess what if
特定于Java EE，但猜猜如果
you have a database server or a web
您有数据库服务器或网站
server that has the same problem right
具有相同问题的服务器
and they produce large images so the
他们会产生大图像，所以
solution of in docker that's been out
已经退出的docker解决方案
for a year and a half now is something
现在已经一年半了
called docker layering okay what that
叫码头工人分层好吗
means is that you don't deploy your
就是说你不部署你的
entire docker image every time what you
每次您都使用整个docker映像
deploy is actually what changed in my in
部署实际上是我的改变
my image right so what this means is you
我的形象正确，这意味着你
can follow essentially the natural model
基本上可以遵循自然模型
that Java EE application servers has in
Java EE应用程序服务器所在的位置
in terms of separation of concerns right
在关注点分离方面
so your infrastructure layer is your app
所以您的基础架构层就是您的应用
server whereas your wire is only the
服务器，而您的电线只是
Delta that you apply on that's the only
您所套用的Delta值是唯一的
thing that's changing in from one docker
一个码头工人正在改变的事情
deployment to the other right so the
部署到另一个权利，因此
initial docker deployment yes so that's
最初的docker部署是的，那是
going to be large because it'll contain
会很大，因为它将包含
the app server and your wire but guess
应用程序服务器和您的线路，但是您猜到了
what subsequent deployments of your of
您的后续部署
your java application server is going to
您的Java应用程序服务器将
be much smaller compared to any other
比其他任何东西都要小
alternatives because your incremental
替代方案，因为您的增量
bit is very clean namely just that just
一点很干净，就是
a war file okay
战争文件好吗
in comparison let's say you're you've
相比之下，假设您是
done some effort to create a fair Jar
做了一些努力来创建一个公平的罐子
solution well guess what
解决方案很好猜
because that fair Jar solution doesn't
因为那个公平的Jar解决方案不会
have the clear demarcation between the
之间有明确的界限
deployment unit and the infrastructure
部署单元和基础架构
you'll actually actually be deploying a
您实际上实际上是在部署
heavier weight docker image every time
每次都有较重的docker映像
you deploy that okay and the same thing
您可以部署相同的东西
happens you know again with docker
发生你再次与码头工人认识
clustering and docker caching all of
集群和docker缓存所有
this because of those capabilities work
因为这些功能起作用
mesh extremely well with Java EE
与Java EE的配合非常好
applications okay
应用还可以
so then there so what what does that
所以那边那是什么
mean so what does this means is you know
是什么意思，这意味着你知道
now we should then evaluate well what if
现在我们应该好好评估一下
you look at docker however if you look
你看码头，但是如果你看
at the docker ecosystem how well does
在Docker生态系统中表现如何
that support Java and it turns out it
支持Java，事实证明
supports Java EE extremely well
很好地支持Java EE
so there's literally docker images
所以实际上是码头工人图像
available of every single Java EE
每个Java EE都可用
platform out there right there there
那里的平台
isn't one that doesn't have a pre-built
不是没有预建的
docker image available that you can just
您可以使用的docker映像
use and run with it and and and keep
使用并运行它，并保持
going with okay so with that in mind I'm
一切顺利，因此我谨记
going to turn it over again to Rodrigo
再把它交给罗德里戈
he's gonna deploy he's gonna show you
他会部署他会告诉你
how to deployed authorized Java EE
如何部署授权的Java EE
images onto a cloud platform alright and
图像到云平台上
this is the result that we were
这就是我们的结果
expecting from the previous deployment
期待以前的部署
right so so as Reza said the first step
对，所以Reza说的第一步
is we need a docker file right so we
是我们需要一个码头工人文件，所以我们
need to get the war file that initially
需要获取最初的战争文件
we you know had in our infrastructure
我们知道我们的基础架构中
deploy to an application server and we
部署到应用服务器，我们
have in this case a blocker file we're
在这种情况下，我们有一个阻止程序文件
going you know in music payara
你会在音乐上知道吗
which by the way announced today they're
顺便说一句，今天他们
the first or one of the first to support
第一个或第一个支持
Java EE 8 so that's you know really
Java EE 8所以您真的知道了
really great and you see three lines of
真的很棒，您会看到三行
code we have no payara
代码我们没有薪水
we have deployment of our file and we
我们已经部署了文件，我们
then you know start our domain this is
那么您知道启动我们的域是
available in github there's a reference
在github上有一个参考
for that and after that you can push
为此，之后您可以推动
your docker image right you create a
您的docker映像就可以创建一个
docker image or darker billdocker tag
docker图像或更暗的billdocker标签
docker push right you need to build it
docker push right，您需要构建它
it constructs the image you need to tag
它会构建您需要标记的图像
so you associate your docker image with
因此您将docker映像与
some destination with some docker
一些码头的一些目的地
registry and then you push that to some
注册表，然后将其推送到一些
darker register in this case we have
在这种情况下较暗的寄存器
that available we're gonna use once
可用的，我们将使用一次
again AWS we're exploring ECS in this
再次，AWS我们正在此方面探索ECS
case this is their ec2 container service
这是他们的ec2容器服务
for the same purpose as kubernetes or
与kubernetes的目的相同或
one of the you know similar it does
您知道类似的一种
offer a container registry so this gets
提供一个容器注册表，这样
started kind of walks you through and
开始有点引导您通过
very nice and easy way to learn and
非常好的和简单的方法来学习和
understand how you can set up and create
了解如何设置和创建
your docker registry so I can come in
您的Docker注册表，以便我可以进入
here and say you know I'm gonna create
在这里说你知道我要创造
my cargo tracker repo do a next step and
我的货物跟踪器仓库执行下一步
it gives you all the information that's
它为您提供了所有的信息
basically a copy and paste and what
基本上是复制和粘贴以及什么
you're gonna do if this is you
如果这是你，你会做
your darker image again locally you
您再次在本地变暗的图像
tagged you push that becomes available
标记为您推送可用
within da de Blasio system or you can
在da de Blasio系统中，或者您可以
expose somewhere else if you want that
如果你想暴露在其他地方
you know if you want so in this case I'm
你知道是否要在这种情况下
not gonna run those steps again for the
不会再为这些步骤运行这些步骤
interest of time but I have done
时间的利益，但我已经做到了
obviously that before and I have already
显然，之前和我已经
my proposed story here I'm gonna cut my
我在这里提出的故事我要剪掉我的
repost or URL and I'm follow with that
重新发布或URL，我跟着
for my next step so once I have my
下一步，所以一旦我有了我的
repository the other thing that I need
存放我需要的其他东西
to think about in AWS terms but you know
用AWS术语考虑，但您知道
in general that that this knowledge II
总的来说，这种知识二
gets transferable anywhere else we need
可以转移到我们需要的其他任何地方
a task definition and what does that
任务定义，这是什么
mean
意思
every time you run a container you need
每次运行容器时，您都需要
to a specify or may want to specify what
指定或可能要指定
parts you were exposing when you do a
当你做一个暴露的部分
darker one you expose parts you mount
较暗的一个会露出安装的零件
volumes to give environmental variables
给出环境变量的体积
so there are set of configurations that
所以有一些配置
you provide along with that docker run
您提供该docker run
that you translate that into a task
您将其转化为任务
definition right so in this case I'm
定义正确，所以在这种情况下，我是
gonna keep since I'm doing part 88 I
因为我正在做第88部分，所以我会保持
will keep that part 88 here obviously
显然会将88部分保留在此处
for more complex deployments you want to
对于您想要的更复杂的部署
let the container Orchestrator to
让容器协调器
identify and dynamically assign a part
识别并动态分配零件
to you you don't want to tie yourself to
对你来说你不想束缚自己
a single port that will bring host
单个端口将带来主机
brutal machine constraints so that open
残酷的机器限制让打开
up a lot of questions the last the next
最后一个问题最多
step is a service so once we have a
步骤是一项服务，所以一旦我们有了
docker container available in a registry
注册表中可用的Docker容器
we define what we need for that to run
我们定义了运行所需的内容
now we have a service that will say you
现在我们有一项服务会告诉您
know keep this guy running I need one
知道让这家伙跑我需要一个
docker run or one container running at
码头工人运行或一个容器在
all times or ten or a hundred so this in
所有的时间或十或一百个
our cases our cargo tracker service I'll
我们的案例我们的货物追踪服务
say that we just need one over here I'm
说我们只需要一个
not gonna put any load balancers or
不会放任何负载平衡器或
anything more complex at this time and
此时任何更复杂的事情，
then with that my search needs to run in
然后我的搜索需要在
a cluster right and that clusters not a
群集权，而不是群集
traditional in a WebLogic cluster or
WebLogic群集中的传统或
application server cluster but it's more
应用服务器集群，但更多
of a think of a higher-level unit where
想起更高层次的单位
you can have multiple services within
您可以在其中拥有多种服务
that cluster and
该集群和
that will orchestrate and coordinate all
将协调和协调所有
the container placement and all of that
容器放置以及所有这些
so in this case here's my cargo trekker
所以这是我的货运龙门
cluster we can specify the size of the
集群，我们可以指定
rittle machines that will be assigned to
将被分配给
that cluster so once you create your you
该集群，因此一旦您创建自己的
know container record trader you you
知道您的集装箱记录交易员
need to give it some computing capacity
需要给它一些计算能力
so it can deploy containers Imraan and
这样就可以部署集装箱Imraan和
whatnot so we're giving here some you
没什么，所以我们在这里给你一些
know CPU memory combination AWS terms
了解CPU内存组合AWS条款
for the instance types we say how many
对于实例类型，我们说多少
of those will assign again I'll give
这些将再次分配，我会给
them a key pair over here as you know
他们是这里的一对钥匙
everybody would we review tasks next
大家接下来我们会审查任务
steps and then we would be able to be in
步骤，然后我们就可以进入
a position to just run it once we run
一旦我们运行就可以运行它的位置
this it's very interesting because this
这很有趣，因为这
you know graphical user interface and
你知道图形用户界面和
just like everything else AWS is exposed
就像AWS暴露的其他一切一样
to API CL is as the case and so you can
视情况而定，因此您可以
automate everything which you should
自动化您应该做的一切
write if you deploy something in a cloud
如果您在云中部署了某些东西，请写
that should be a hundred percent
那应该是百分之一百
automated and they have something that's
自动化，他们有一些
called cloud formation and behind the
称为云的形成和背后的
scenes cloud formation is managing and
场景云形成正在管理和
creating out the orchestration of those
创造那些的编排
services for you I have one cluster here
为您服务我这里有一个集群
already set up I have my cargo tracker
已经设置好了，我有我的货物追踪器
service you can see that I have given
你可以看到我给的服务
one brutal machine associate to it and
一台残酷的机器与之相关
since I told it to run one service I can
因为我告诉它运行一项服务，所以我可以
come in here and say that there is one
来这里说有一个
blocker which it SS cause a task and
它造成了任务的拦截器，并且
from that task I can get all of its
从那个任务中我可以得到所有的
details and eventually I get to D you
细节，最后我去找你
know application so let's see if this
知道应用程序，所以让我们看看
time I'm gonna have more looks so that
到时候我会看起来更多
works perfect right so I have packaged
完美的作品，所以我已经打包
with PI R as you saw before I saw before
我之前见过的PI R
and if I do cargo tracker here's my
如果我做货物追踪器，这是我的
application once again you know
再次申请，你知道
available and an easy to run is to use
可用，易于使用
as well as it would be the console at me
以及我的控制台
okay the next stop is
好吧，下一站是
platform-as-a-service so as I said the
正如我所说，平台即服务
distinction between pairs with images
图像对之间的区别
and docker and really pairs is and pairs
和码头工人，真正的对是和对
at this point is that it that image is
在这一点上，它是图像
built in as very closely into a UI right
非常紧密地内置在UI中
so you don't have to do anything else
所以你不必做任何其他事情
just natively supports whatever
只是本地支持
application server that is and in many
和许多应用服务器
cases actually the application server
实际应用服务器
it's always implicit so whenever you're
它总是隐式的，所以无论何时
using that that solution it's just
使用那个解决方案就是
implied that you're using that
暗示您正在使用
particular application server and that
特定的应用服务器以及
cuts down some of the boilerplate and
减少一些样板
some of the additional steps that you
您需要执行的一些其他步骤
would need if you weren't using pass
如果您不使用通行证则需要
solution so basically what happens here
解决方案，所以这里基本上会发生什么
is that your deployment unit really
是您的部署部门真的
becomes just point and click setup your
成为只是点，然后单击设置您的
server and you just deploy your war file
服务器，您只需部署您的war文件
and that's your that's your basically
那就是你那基本上就是你
your deployment unit typically though it
部署单元通常
will come with some kind of console
将带有某种控制台
access that you can manage your
您可以管理您的访问权限
application with and of course again you
申请，当然您也可以
get in a lot of Java e-pass solutions
加入很多Java e-pass解决方案
available
有空
openshift Oracle cloud bluemix jelastic
openshift Oracle云Bluemix Jelastic
nhip also again i'm gonna skip over the
小憩也再次我要跳过
pros and cons i think it's a little
优点和缺点我认为这有点
unless maybe besides the point
除非也许不是重点
so that we can get to the demo and where
这样我们就可以进行演示了
you can kind of dig in into a bit more
您可以进一步挖掘更多
of the details here alright so shifting
这里的细节还好，所以转移了
gears now and we're going with jelastic
现在齿轮，我们将与jelastic一起
anyone here familiar with jelastic great
这里的任何人都熟悉jelastic great
several several hands up I think
我想几手
jelastic you know it's close but I think
jelastic，你知道它很近但是我想
it's fantastic right it's it's it's so
太好了，是这样
easy to set up something I never heard
容易设置我从未听说过的东西
I've never heard before to be honest
老实说，我从未听说过
I've never used it before and as and I
我以前从未使用过它
think it's that's what I want for our
认为这就是我想要的
law provided that's what I want thrown
法律规定这就是我要抛出的内容
kind of a platform something that I can
一种平台，我可以
look and easily get started right so
外观，轻松入门，因此
they have the concept of you can import
他们有你可以导入的概念
environments you can export the
您可以导出的环境
environments they also have a
他们也有一个环境
marketplace where you can you know
您可以知道的市场
leverage pre-configured environments in
利用以下环境中的预配置环境
this case we're gonna go with a new
这种情况下，我们要去一个新的
environment and just like with payara
环境，就像payara
jelastic is also supporting je8
jelastic也支持je8
so that
以便
you know phenomenal what I want to show
你知道我想表现的惊人
here is they have support obviously for
这显然是他们的支持
Java and in a PHP if someone's
Java和PHP（如果有人）
interesting PHP they have docker and
有趣的PHP，他们有docker和
other stuff but look at this UI right
其他的东西，但看看这个UI吧
what we're seeing here is word we can
我们在这里看到的是我们可以
define and we can use a good selection
定义，我们可以使用一个很好的选择
of application servers on the Java
Java上的应用程序服务器数量
ecosystem you know they have GlassFish
你知道他们有GlassFish的生态系统
they have JBoss payara and and many
他们有JBoss payara，还有很多
others right so this is really good it's
其他人对，所以这真的很好
not something that you find in every
不是你在每个地方都能找到的东西
single call provider but with that said
单一呼叫提供商，但说
up here I'm gonna be no pickup payara I
在这里，我将不再是皮卡帕拉我
want to get the latest version of payara
想要获取最新版本的payara
it's loading as you can see here I'm
如你所见我正在加载
getting a JDK 8 its latest version of
获得JDK 8的最新版本
payara if it brings you here on this
payara，如果它把你带到这里
middle box can can you see that well let
中间的盒子你能看到那好吗
me let me give him more right so if you
我让我给他更多权利，如果你
look at this middle box here it's
看看这中间的盒子
already out of the box gives you
开箱即用
scalability so you can have vertical
可扩展性，因此您可以拥有垂直
scalability which is basically you know
可扩展性，基本上你知道
how much memory and CPU you're gonna
你要多少内存和CPU
allocate from the beginning right so you
从一开始就分配，所以你
know in this case I'm saying you know
知道在这种情况下我是说你知道
I'll give you 3 gig of memory with this
我会给你3G的记忆
much CPU and you can grow up to a
很多CPU，您可以成长为
certain level so if your application
一定水平，所以如果您的应用程序
under load is under load your your
在负载下在负载下
computing capacity and you know increase
计算能力，你知道增加
with you and at the same time down below
与您同时在下方
it's also providing horizontal
它也提供水平
scalability so again if you have one
可伸缩性
node or if you need multiple nodes it's
节点，或者如果您需要多个节点，
just a matter of you know defining what
只需您知道定义什么
do you want right the interesting part
你想要正确的部分吗
here is if you know it's it also once I
如果你知道的话，这也是我一次
add more than one node it created for me
添加为我创建的多个节点
that abstract that that extra layer for
那抽象的那一层
load balance are adding an engine X load
负载平衡正在增加引擎X负载
balancer thought so that's very handy
平衡器认为，这非常方便
and very helpful you know especially for
尤其对您有帮助
those that already have workloads
那些已经有工作量的
running on-premises there's a high
在本地运行有一个很高的
chance we're doing this with nginx or a
机会我们用nginx或a
similar kind of proxy load balancer
类似的代理负载均衡器
solution so that's it's very good they
解决方案，所以这是非常好的
also have some interesting you know that
也有一些有趣的你知道
they offer you the cost as well which I
他们也向您提供费用，我
think it's valuable and it's useful out
认为这很有价值，而且很有用
of the box they have some variables as I
盒子里有一些变量
mentioned on the part of the exporting
在出口部分提到
the environment so there is a
环境，所以有一个
pre-configured environment installation
预先配置的环境安装
set
组
process here that will automatically put
在这里自动处理
your PI R or GlassFish in cluster mode
群集模式下的PI R或GlassFish
so before on the other two options we
所以在其他两个选项之前
were looking at we would have to do that
在看着我们将不得不这样做
have lifting ourselves right so this is
有提升自己的权利，所以这是
you know comes very it's very good and
你知道这非常好
you would have an environment name you
您将拥有一个环境名称
can give that environment name set up so
可以设置该环境名称
DNS and whatnot one other thing you can
DNS和您可以做的另一件事
you know connect your application
你知道连接你的应用程序
through maven in this case I have the
通过Maven在这种情况下，我有
cargo track or war file here I can click
货物追踪或战争档案，我可以点击
on it I have a cup of environments
在上面我有一个环境
preset up and I can define it
预设，我可以定义它
understands it's a warrior app it
知道这是一个战士应用程序
understands it can be deployed to that
知道可以部署到
specific environment so again it's it's
特定的环境，再次是
the same operation as you would do going
与您将要执行的操作相同
to you know console at the means saying
你知道控制台的意思是
deployed war file so that also becomes
部署的战争文件，因此也成为
very very handy the piece that I want to
我想要的东西非常方便
show you is that I mention I have one
告诉你我提到我有一个
pre-configure instance over here let's
在这里预先配置实例
go to it which is the one that I
去那是我的那一个
mentioned about the auto clustering user
提到有关自动集群用户
and password and I just kind of want to
和密码，我只是想
show that because I think again it's it
证明那是因为我再想一遍
does it does add value as we are going
它确实会在我们前进的过程中增加价值吗
through this so you're looking at the
通过这个，所以你正在看
you know payara
你知道payara
as you see there is a cluster here set
如您所见，这里有一个集群
up and I have I didn't have to do
起，我有我不必做
anything and then down the road you can
任何东西，然后就可以了
deploy your application either through
通过以下方式部署应用程序
you know the web console or you can just
您知道网络控制台，也可以
come in here and you know select the war
来到这里，你知道选择战争
and deploy in addition to that it also
并部署它
gives some of the Messam metrics
提供了一些Messam指标
oops this is the topology but it does
哎呀，这是拓扑，但确实
give some really nice metrics that you
给出一些非常好的指标，
can start analyzing what's happening
可以开始分析发生了什么
behind the scenes it opens you something
在幕后它为您打开了一些东西
that's interesting it gives you access
有趣的是它使您可以访问
to some of the files from a folder
到文件夹中的某些文件
structure perspective so again overall
整体的结构视角
with this with the previous approach you
与以前的方法一起使用
know we when we did darker we had to
知道我们黑暗时，我们不得不
create a docker file we had to have a
创建一个docker文件，我们必须有一个
quick learn a little bit about a
快速了解一点
container orchestrate and whatnot and in
容器编排和其他内容
this case we didn't have to change
在这种情况下，我们不必更改
anything our application it remains to
我们剩下的任何应用程序
be a war file right
成为战争文件吧
and the infrastructure knowledge was
基础设施知识是
very minimal so I think that you know
非常少，所以我想你知道
adds a lot of value for those that want
为那些想要的人增加很多价值
to explore and go take that path to the
探索并走那条路
cloud okay
云好
moving forward so although most cloud
因此前进，尽管大多数云
providers out there when they're talking
提供者在谈话时
about Java support um they have some way
关于Java支持，他们有一些方法
of installing an application server
安装应用程序服务器的过程
either through a docker image or a
通过泊坞窗映像或
native image that they that they build
他们建立的本机图像
or it's built into the platform like in
或像
jelastic space however there are a small
弹性空间但是很小
number of cloud providers out there that
那里的云提供商数量
don't provide that flexibility the only
没有唯一的灵活性
thing they support is really either
他们支持的是
Tomcat or jetty or here you go here's
Tomcat或码头，或者您在这里
your jdk environment and that's all you
您的jdk环境，仅此而已
get right and then you have to build in
正确，然后您必须建立
the rest of your applications based off
其余应用程序基于
of that
在那
right so there aren't a whole lot of
对，所以没有很多
these really the big the only ones that
这些真的很大，只有那些
have this sort of restrictive
有这种限制
environment is Heroku and GAE well
环境是Heroku和GAE都很好
obviously in this situation all of the
显然在这种情况下
other solutions that we talked about are
我们讨论的其他解决方案是
isn't going to work because they all
因为他们都不能上班
entail some kind of installation or some
需要某种安装或某种
kind of reconfiguration of an
一种重新配置
application server that's not going to
不会使用的应用程序服务器
be possible in this case however what
在这种情况下是可能的，但是
you can do here is actually not depend
你可以在这里做实际上是不依赖
on that because now you have all of
之所以这样，是因为现在您拥有了所有
these Java EE nice Java if you are
这些Java EE不错的Java（如果您是
solutions that you can just create a jar
您可以创建一个罐子的解决方案
as opposed to a war file and deploy that
而不是战争文件并部署
on top of a bare-metal JVM okay so I'm
在裸机JVM之上，所以我
gonna do a little bit different in the
会在
interest of time here and this is gonna
时间的兴趣在这里，这将会
be a little bit of a surprise for for
有点惊喜
Ryan the only reason I'm doing this to
我这样做的唯一原因是瑞安
him is because I know he can handle it
他是因为我知道他可以应付
sir
先生
so I'm gonna surely just talk about our
所以我一定要说说我们的
final deck here which is our resources
这是我们的最终资源
okay and then I'm gonna actually hand it
好的，然后我要交给它
over to Ryan for majority of the rest of
剩下的大部分交给瑞安
this time that we have which is we have
这次我们拥有的是
about 10 more minutes left so what we've
还有大约10分钟的时间
done here is try to give you a really
在这里做的是尝试给你一个真正的
good starting point for getting started
入门的好起点
on the cloud with Java applications
使用Java应用程序在云上
they're your best resource actually is
他们是你最好的资源
the
的
github repository that that that Rodrigo
那个Rodrigo的github仓库
showed he actually have has specific
表明他实际上有特定的
instructions on each other cloud
彼此之间的指令云
platforms and some that we didn't show
平台和一些我们未展示的平台
step-by-step instructions on how to get
有关如何获取的分步说明
started on those in addition to that
从那些开始
there's some that obviously we didn't
有些显然我们没有
have time to cover right so the nice
有时间掩盖正确，所以很好
thing about it is I did actually did do
事情是我确实做了
some research and try to find point
一些研究并试图找到要点
references on those particular cloud
那些特定云上的引用
environments of how do you set up Java
您如何设置Java的环境
EE in those particular environment
在那些特定环境中的EE
similar to what perhaps what Rodrigo
类似于什么罗德里戈
would have written up you know in in his
会在他的身上写下你知道的
github repository so those are some
github存储库，所以有些
additional resources in addition to what
除了什么之外的其他资源
you have with with Rodriguez our github
与Rodriguez一起使用我们的github
repository a final word that I'm gonna
储存我要说的最后一句话
say if I don't get to say anything else
说如果我不说其他话
because of time is that you know
因为时间是你知道
basically our aim here is to get you
基本上，我们的目的是让您
started on on running Java applications
开始运行Java应用程序
on the cloud as quickly as possible and
尽快在云上
give you you can you can use all of the
给你，你可以使用所有的
resources that we already went and
我们已经去过的资源
created so many man-hours to create so
创造了如此多的工时
you can utilize that and of course for
你可以利用它，当然
those of you who are speakers please
那些演讲者请
consider delivering this talk we made
考虑发表我们的演讲
and talked such that you can just take
并这样说，你可以
him and run and deliver this talk so
他并跑着讲这个话
with that I am going to hand it over to
我将把它交给
Ryan probably for the rest of this talk
瑞安在本讲余下的时间里可能
and I will tell you this is what he has
我会告诉你这就是他所拥有的
is probably worth a talk on its own
可能值得自己演讲
right so really not doing brands Ryan
对，所以真的不做品牌瑞安
just as here Thanks so now that we got
就像这里，谢谢，所以现在我们
that out of the way I guess I'm cleared
我想我已经清除了
to talk to seven right actually actually
其实和七个人说话
this was so simple that it I can I had
这是如此简单，我可以
to make this longer because it's so
使它更长，因为它是如此
quick to actually deploy the application
快速实际部署应用程序
this is actually easier than I thought
这实际上比我想象的要容易
it would be prior to working on this
这将是在此之前
presentation I hadn't actually used
我实际上没有使用过的演示文稿
Heroku previously thinking that it was
Heroku以前以为是
had been at conferences where it was
曾经在会议上
primarily Ruby developers that were
主要是Ruby开发人员
using it so I thought it was a ruby
使用它，所以我认为这是一个红宝石
platform but that's not the case it's
平台，但事实并非如此
actually a very good job of platform
平台真的很好
Java eight and installed it's a little
Java 8并安装了一点
bit different than the the stuff that
与其他东西有些不同
we've looked at before in that in order
我们已经按顺序看过了
to push your code up there you actually
将代码实际推到那里
use git so you'll actually push use get
使用git，所以您实际上将推送使用get
to push the code to it or you can have
将代码推送到它，否则您可以拥有
it tied into your git repository so that
它绑定到您的git存储库中，以便
every time you push code it pulls from
每次您推送代码时都会从中提取
you does the sync and pulls down for you
您进行同步并为您下拉
it does support add-ons and it's got a
它确实支持附加组件，并且有一个
number of add-ons of you know it has
您知道的附加组件数量
like database add-ons pre-configured so
像预先配置的数据库附加组件一样
that you can get up and running quickly
您可以快速启动并运行
it has RabbitMQ which I won't be using
它有RabbitMQ，我将不会使用
for this presentation it does support
对于此演示文稿，它确实支持
process scaling everything runs in
过程扩展一切运行
isolation it's got a very nice logging
隔离，它有一个很好的日志记录
infrastructure so that on the command
基础设施，以便在命令上
line on your computer you can get the
行在您的计算机上，您可以
logging back so it's very developer
重新登录，因此非常开发
centric in my opinion it does have a
我认为以中心为中心
free tier for experimentation and then a
免费试用，然后
hobby level that's one step up which
爱好水平是一步
basically doesn't sleep but it doesn't
基本上不睡觉，但是不睡觉
put it to sleep after thirty minutes it
三十分钟后让它睡觉
starts with around 512 Meg's of RAM
从大约512 Meg的RAM开始
allocated to the app that your Java
分配给您的Java的应用程序
process gets allocated so dependent upon
进程被分配，因此取决于
your application that you're deploying
您正在部署的应用程序
you may need to actually move to the
您可能需要实际移至
paid tier if it's a larger Java EE
如果是较大的Java EE，则为付费层
application or parts thereof the
应用或其部分
previous part of this presentation we
本演示的前一部分
focused payara the full server in this
将payara集中在此的完整服务器上
part of the presentation I'm actually
我实际上是演讲的一部分
gonna look at PI or a micro because
会看PI或微型，因为
we're only able to basically deploy a
我们基本上只能部署一个
jar file to the server we can actually
jar文件到服务器，我们实际上可以
copy up a full server although I think
复制完整的服务器，尽管我认为
there are ways of getting around that
有一些解决方法
where you could check GlassFish into
您可以在其中检查GlassFish
your get repository and pull it down
您的存储库并将其下拉
that way but I wouldn't recommend that
这样，但我不建议
with pyrrha is it's actually it's pyro
与pyrrha是它实际上是pyro
or you could have done this I actually
否则你可能已经做到了
had a separate demo that I was working
有一个我正在工作的单独演示
on let's warm micro so you could do it
让我们温暖微，所以你可以做到
with either of these two Pyro's nice
这两个Pyro都不错
than that it was easy to get up and
比起起床容易
running within a couple of minutes it
在几分钟内运行
implements the if you're not familiar
如果您不熟悉，则实施
it Eclipse implements the Eclipse micro
Eclipse实现了Eclipse micro
profile about 70 Meg's in size and
配置文件约70兆的大小和
you've get all of the services that I've
您已经获得了我所提供的所有服务
listed down there by default the
默认情况下，
documentation is a little off right now
文档现在有点少了
in that I say EJ be light and EJ be
我说EJ要轻，EJ要
light means that you don't get message
灯亮表示您未收到任何消息
driven bean 's they actually do support
驱动bean的确支持
message driven bean z' so hopefully
消息驱动bean z'如此希望
they'll get their documentation updated
他们将更新他们的文档
soon since this was so simple I had to
很快，因为这是如此简单，所以我不得不
make it a little bit harder so I decided
让它变得更难一点，所以我决定
to pull in AWS so with pyro pyro micro
用pyro pyro micro拉入AWS
you don't get open mq by default so you
您默认情况下不会打开mq，因此您
don't have a JMS provider fukusa
没有JMS提供者fukusa
provides RabbitMQ as an add-on however
提供RabbitMQ作为附加组件
there is no AR AR file resource adapter
没有AR AR文件资源适配器
available to plug into GlassFish or
可插入GlassFish或
dnia any other app container so in
dénia任何其他应用程序容器
order to use message driven bean z' I
为了使用消息驱动的bean z'I
needed to find another solution so what
需要找到另一个解决方案
I did was I used payara has a
我曾经做过，我曾经使用过payara
proof-of-concept RER adapter for amazon
用于亚马逊的概念验证RER适配器
sqs the amazon's queuing system which
sqs亚马逊的排队系统
meant that all i had to do was create
意味着我要做的就是创造
the queues up on amazon and then add
在亚马逊上排队，然后添加
them to my code the cargo trapper
根据我的代码，他们是货物捕手
application thus i'll show the
应用程序，因此我将展示
modifications that I made to the cargo
我对货物进行的修改
track for modifications application thus
跟踪修改申请，因此
far all the demos so far there been no
到目前为止，所有演示都没有
changes to the actual application this
更改为实际应用
time I actually had to make changes one
我实际上不得不做出改变的时间
to get the cargo tracker off of open MQ
使货物跟踪器脱离开放式MQ
because they had hard-coded settings in
因为他们在其中进行了硬编码设置
there I'm to be unless that was the
除非那是我
primary primary changes that I made to
我对主要的主要更改
it and then the second one was to adjust
然后第二个是调整
it for using the payara sqs plugin RER
用于使用payara sqs插件RER
file so that's basically that so
文件，基本上就是这样
starting off this was the initial open
开始这是最初的开放
MQ MDB code so I'm basically showing so
MQ MDB代码，所以我基本上是这样显示的
this is the starting code where we have
这是我们拥有的起始代码
our message driven we have our
我们的信息驱动我们有我们的
destination lookups everything for open
目的地查找一切开放
MQ and when I change it over to using
MQ，当我将其更改为使用时
the code that the the the AR AR you have
您所拥有的AR AR的代码
to change the code a little I have to
更改代码我不得不
change the message driven bean a little
稍微改变消息驱动的bean
bit to make it work with the
一点使其与
payara sqs are sqs adapter so some of
payara sqs是sqs适配器，所以一些
the changes I had to change it to Amazon
我必须将其更改为Amazon的更改
asked us listener if you implement
问我们听众是否实施
message listener it actually tries to
消息监听器实际上试图
fire up they actually tries to look up
开火他们实际上试图抬头
em open em cube which is not actually
em打开实际上不是的em多维数据集
installed in Harrah's out it took me a
安装在哈拉的外面，这花了我一个
while to figure out that that's why the
而要弄清楚这就是为什么
application wasn't actually running
应用程序实际上并未运行
because I was like like you know I was
因为我就像你知道我是
checking I thought I had left a file
检查我以为我已经离开了文件
around somewhere I've removed all of the
我已经删除了所有
access keys obviously for the
显然，访问键
presentation right now they don't have
现在他们没有的演示文稿
any there's not an easier way of getting
没有什么比这更简单的方法了
them in there and then the you annotator
他们在那里，然后你注释
receive message with on sqs message to
接收带有on sqs消息的消息至
receive the message and then in the web
收到消息，然后在网络上
that XML remove all the references for
该XML删除了所有的引用
open mq which is just a delete don't
打开只是删除的mq
have to add anything in there and then
必须在那里添加任何东西，然后
so the application deploys on the route
因此应用程序将部署在路由上
remove cargo tracker so that you can
卸下货物追踪器，以便您可以
just go to the the when you open the
只需在打开时
application that you don't have to open
您不必打开的应用程序
another site to then navigate to the
另一个网站，然后导航到
cargo track or application slash cargo
货物跟踪或应用程序削减货物
tracker so it just makes it open on the
跟踪器，因此它只是使其在
root of the application the other so the
应用程序的根
changes cargo tracker has one class that
更改货物跟踪器具有一类
basically dispatches events to open MQ
基本上调度事件以打开MQ
so that class required a little bit of
所以这个课需要一点
shame a few changes so this was the Java
丢了一些更改，所以这是Java
EE 7 code for connecting up with the
EE 7代码，用于与
queues this was the changed code I was
排队这是我被更改的代码
sorry this was the code for sending a
抱歉，这是发送邮件的代码
message where it's using the JMS context
使用JMS上下文的消息
to send it all standards so this is the
发送所有标准，所以这是
revamped code to use sqs so as you can
修改代码以使用sqs
see I have to put I add that connection
看到我必须添加我的连接
factor up at the top initiative a
最重要的一项
resource look upon the sqs connection
资源查看sqs连接
factory and configure it in the
工厂并在
constructor and then the method method
构造函数，然后是方法method
for sending a message right now they
他们现在发送消息
only support sending text messages so I
只支持发送短信，所以我
had to adjust some of the code in there
必须在那里调整一些代码
that was sending objects to actually
那实际上是在发送对象
convert them to text the deployment
将它们转换为文本部署
steps are fairly simple you install the
步骤很简单，您安装
Heroku SDK locally on your computer and
您计算机上本地的Heroku SDK，以及
this gives you a command line to execute
这给你一个命令行来执行
commands so the first one first one you
命令，所以第一个第一个你
execute is actually Heroku loggin which
执行实际上是Heroku loggin
then sets up a session is like doing the
然后设置一个会话就像
AWS login for the first time on your
您第一次使用AWS登录
local machine so you don't have to login
本地计算机，因此您不必登录
for all the subsequent commands to
对于所有后续命令
create an application you do who create
创建您创建的应用程序
if you don't provide a name it makes up
如果您不提供名字，则由它组成
something random for you you add a proc
随机的东西为您添加一个过程
file with a command line to invoke your
带有命令行的文件来调用您的
application you then commit your changes
应用程序，然后提交更改
locally to get and you do a git push to
在本地获取，然后您进行git push
Haruko
春子
so you just say get pushed to Haruko
所以你只是说被推向晴子
command line has already set everything
命令行已经设置了所有内容
up and your code actually what Haruka
和您的代码实际上是什么
does at this point was it pulls from
在这一点上是从
your yet it takes the code that you
您的代码却需要您
pushed to it and it doesn't even build
推到它，它甚至没有建立
over there so it actually builds the
在那边，所以它实际上建立了
code it's not you're not deploying build
代码不是您没有在部署构建
code you're deploying the source code
您正在部署源代码的代码
file and then it builds it and runs it
文件，然后将其构建并运行
right so it's clean you don't have to
对，所以很干净，您不必
worry about something you know is cached
担心您知道的东西被缓存了
output on your local machine anything up
在本地计算机上输出任何东西
there so after you've done that you you
在那之后，你就可以
can scale it up so I start up one dynamo
可以扩大规模，所以我可以启动一个发电机
to get going and then you do who go open
去走，然后你去打开谁
to open the application and then finally
打开应用程序，然后最后
if you want to see the logs you do log
如果您想查看日志，请登录
slash tail now that I mentioned the proc
斜线尾巴，现在我提到了过程
file the proc file is the magic that
归档proc文件是魔术
makes us all work so but at the
使我们所有人都这样工作，但在
beginning I have the the web colon that
开始，我有了网络冒号
tells it that it's a web application so
告诉它这是一个Web应用程序
it's actually gonna make sure that I
实际上是要确保我
bind to the port so if I don't if my app
绑定到端口，所以如果我不绑定我的应用程序
starts up and it doesn't bind to the web
启动并没有绑定到网络
court that's expected then it will say
预期的法院然后会说
that the startup failed and it will kill
启动失败，它将终止
it so this is the command line for
所以这是命令行
starting up Mike pyro micro I do Java
启动Mike pyro micro我做Java
dash jar IR a micro that's the pyro
仪表盘IR微型就是发火的
that's the entire GlassFish application
这就是整个GlassFish应用程序
server in one jar file I do - - port and
我在一个jar文件中处理服务器--端口和
the dollar sign port is the environment
美元符号端口就是环境
variable that the port that the that
变量那个那个那个的端口
Haruka wants it to start up on it's not
遥想让它开始不是
gonna be port 80 and as I'm gonna be
将要成为80端口，而我将成为
port 8080 it's gonna be some port that
端口8080将会是一些端口
they made up great they're gonna be
他们组成了伟大的他们将成为
looking to make sure that you Bowden are
希望确保您的鲍登是
serving up content on that I deploy the
在我部署的内容上提供内容
AR AR file and then I deploy the track
AR AR文件，然后部署轨道
of war and as you can see I've got the
战争，正如您所看到的，
target slash cargo tracker dot war so
目标斜线货运跟踪器点战争如此
I'm pulling the code that isn't built so
我正在提取未构建的代码
I pushed it they built the code the war
我推动了他们建立了战争的代码
file is in the output and now I run it
文件在输出中，现在我运行它
and that's basically the demo we're out
这基本上就是我们要演示的演示
of
的
I'm but that's you know if you can have
我是，但是那是你知道你是否可以拥有
your application pushed and running up
您的应用程序已推送并运行
there at no time at all if you go
如果你去那里根本没有任何时间
through their Administrative Council you
通过他们的行政会议，您
can set up SSL certificates you can
可以设置SSL证书
easily add on stuff on to it so it's
轻松在上面添加内容
really easy I had to make it more
真的很容易，我不得不做得更多
complicated make it longer I'm doing the
复杂会使我做的更长
spin up the application sorry
旋转应用程序抱歉
yeah nothing like living dangerously
是的，没有什么比危险的生活
yeah and the one thing I will say so
是的，我会说的一句话
okay
好的
I never do this okay so the first thing
我从来没有这样做，所以第一件事
I have to do is do a Heroku push and
我要做的就是做一个Heroku推送
what you're gonna see is the output from
您将看到的是来自的输出
the server Oh everything is up-to-date
服务器哦，一切都是最新的
there's nothing to push um so it's
没有什么可以推的，所以
actually already running
实际上已经在运行
um if I was if I was creating a new app
嗯，如果我正在创建一个新的应用程序
I would do who go
我会去谁
oh great was going to create so this is
哦，伟大的将要创建，所以这是
creating another a pop up on Haruko
在Haruko上创建另一个弹出窗口
which I'm not on that push to okay so
我不打算这样做，所以
another app is done the app name is
完成另一个应用程序，应用程序名称为
actually still they created this random
实际上他们还是随机创造了
name still rich I can now push my local
名字仍然很丰富，我现在可以推送本地
because I have my Co doesn't get locally
因为我的公司不在本地
so I'm pushing everything since a date
所以自约会以来我一直在推动一切
and I can do it's actually already
我已经可以做到了
running so you gonna good to see a run
跑步，所以你会很高兴看到跑步
the application should be running okay
该应用程序应该可以正常运行
well let's up and running basically in
好吧，让我们基本上在
summary next time somebody says Hawaii
下次有人说夏威夷时的摘要
doesn't work on the cloud please call
无法在云上运行，请致电
don't walk on it
不要在上面走
Java he works on the cloud extremely
他在云上工作的Java非常丰富
well honestly there's lots of more
老实说，还有很多
options and just about anything else and
选项，以及几乎所有其他内容，
please on the way on your way out leave
请在出门途中离开
us some good feedback you know lots of
我们提供了一些很好的反馈，您知道很多
lots of hours and lots of personal
很多小时，很多个人
sacrifices to make this demo happen so
为了使这个演示发生而做出了牺牲
please support help us out by giving
请给予支持以帮助我们
some feedback and to get the logs when
一些反馈，并在何时获取日志
something doesn't work right we do
有些事情行不通，我们做
hiroko logs - - tail or the number it's
hiroko日志--尾巴或数字
just the standard tale thing and there
只是标准的故事而已
we can see all of our logs so I was able
我们可以看到所有日志，因此我能够
to pulling back the logs for what's
撤回什么日志
actually executing up on the server so
实际上在服务器上执行了
you can actually see the app is
您实际上可以看到该应用程序是
deploying right now we're still
现在部署，我们仍然
deploying what's actually instantiating
部署实际实例化的东西
the Derby database there we go
我们去的Derby数据库
now
现在
there we go try the tracker
在那里，我们尝试跟踪器
so that's running and it's sucking too
所以它正在运行，也很烂
if we start executing actions the
如果我们开始执行动作
queuing stuff will be handled by Amazon
排队的东西将由亚马逊处理
okay thank you very much I appreciate it
好的，非常感谢，我很感激
like thanks for patience hopefully this
希望感谢您的耐心等待
was useful thank you
很有用，谢谢
[Applause]
[掌声]